Guide to the William R. George family papers, 1750-1989.
George, William R. family papers, 1750-1989.
- Series XI. Clippings
  - Clippings., 1980 (Box 143, Folder 52)
  - Clippings., 1981 (Box 143, Folder 53)
  - Clippings., 1982 (Box 143, Folder 54)
  - Clippings., 1983 (Box 143, Folder 55)
  - Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 143, Folder 56)
  - Undated clippings and miscellaneous documents (Box 144)
  - Undated clippings re: W.R.G., n.d. (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Undated clippings re: G.J.R. (Freeville)., n.d. (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Undated clippings re: other Junior Republics, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Undated clippings re: related ideas (e.g. Junior Municipality)., n.d. (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Undated clippings re: ex-citizens, relatives, friends, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Undated clippings re: Child Labor Amendment, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Undated clippings re: social welfare, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Undated clippings re: political and national issues, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Undated clippings re: miscellaneous and fragments, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Lists of citizens, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 10-12)
  - Lists of addresses of friends, ex-citizens, etc., n.d. (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous lists, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - Collected business cards, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous songs and poems, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Religious publications and announcements, 1873-1884 (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - Papers from Mrs. Daddy's Bible, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - Miscellany, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - Annotations re: collection, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous printed items re GJR, 1940-1970 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - The Adult Minor, by Willam R. George, 1937 (Box 187)
  - The Hunter, 1941 (Box 187)
  - The Hunter, 1942 (Box 187)
  - Class of 1970, 1970 (Box 187)
- Series XII. Wax Recordings
  - 9 wax cylinder recordings (Box 145)
  - 9 wax recordings (Box 146)
  - 9 wax recordings (Box 147)
  - 9 wax recordings (Box 148)
  - 9 wax recordings (Box 149)
  - 12 wax recordings (Box 150)
- Series XIII. Oral History Transcripts
  - A. Alvord Baker, 1965; transcript 1183
  - Mrs. Georgia Fellows, 1965; transcript 1184
  - Malcolm Freeborn, 1965; transcript 1185
  - Mrs. Albert B. Genung, 1965; transcript 1186
  - John J. Kinane, 1965; transcript 1187
- Series XIV. Malcolm J. Freeborn Papers (Box 151)